Is the general meeting's agenda
about the introduction
of a teacher review process
for joining the student council?
They're pinpointing me,
who has a bad impression with teachers,
and launching an all-out attack.
Are you really going to do it?
It won't do you guys any merit, right?
Yes, it will.
If I defeat her,
my reputation
as a presidential candidate will go up.
Besides,
she insulted Kuze and me.
I want her to retract her words
and apologize sincerely,
or I can't take it.
I see.
However, it's not all bad.
We can use this chance
to make an appearance
before the closing ceremony speech.
If you put it that way,
I can't say anything else.
All right.
Let's spread the news today.
President, I'll make the flyers.
Okay, I'm counting on you.
Masachika, Alya,
do your best.
Yes, thank you.
Okay.
Anyway, based on the current trends,
Taniyama would make this claim.
I see.
Based on this prediction,
how would you refute it?
Well, not bad.
But we still need to organize
the contents of the claim.
Hey, Kuze.
Kuze, are you
on bad terms with Taniyama?
No.
I don't think so.
I think we respect each other a lot.
We got along well in junior high.
I see.
Well then, why did Taniyama do that?
Well, about that.
She probably thinks
that I'm disrupting the election for fun.
Then right from the start,
why did she have this misunderstanding?
I was originally Yuki's partner.
But now, I parted ways with Yuki
who has the highest support
and joined forces with another candidate.
It's only natural
that she thinks I'm messing around.
That's...
So because I paired up with Kuze,
this happened to him?
I'm...
Alya?
What's wrong?
I'll do my best tomorrow.
Yes, you can do it.
Kuzecchi, it's been a while.
I'll be in your care today.
No, that didn't sound right either.
Hey, how can you be so relaxed?
After all, I'm not going to present
in the general meeting.
Of course, I'm relaxed.
Hello, I'm Nonoa Miyamae.
You can say I'm Sayacchi's partner.
I'm Alisa Kujou.
Let's have a meaningful discussion.
How serious of you.
I feel like you'll surprisingly
get along with Sayacchi.
Was that really Taniyama's partner?
Yes, they seem to be childhood friends.
Their personalities
and temperaments differ,
but they're still very close.
I see.
Besides, Miyamae
is at the top of the school hierarchy.
In terms of connections,
she's definitely one
of the best in school.
In the election,
that's indeed a threat.
But don't worry about that now.
Just focus on dealing with Taniyama today.
You're right. I understand.
What do you think about this agenda?
It's hard to say.
Speaking of Taniyama,
she competed with that rich girl
for the junior high presidency, right?
I heard her opponent
is a transfer student?
All I know is that she has good grades.
Can I really do it?
Will I be rejected by everyone again
just like back then?
No, I have to do it.
It's also for the sake
of my partner, Kuze.
Can she really make a speech?
Taniyama will win for sure.
...ya.
Alya.
Kuze.
Are you really an E cup?
What?
Pervert!
What are you talking about
in this situation?
I can ask you this
precisely because of this situation.
You can't hit me now, right?
Just die already.
Is that how you look at trash?
Do you feel less nervous now?
Alya.
Who is your opponent?
Isn't it Taniyama?
No.
Your opponent
is that ideal,
perfect version of yourself.
So,
just think about how to portray
the coolest version of yourself.
Don't worry.
If anything happens,
I'll take care of everything.
It's time.
We will now begin the general meeting.
The proposers are Sayaka Taniyama
and Nonoa Miyamae.
The opposers are Alisa Kujou
and Masachika Kuze.
The agenda
is the introduction
of a teacher review process
for joining the student council.
Now, proposition,
please present your arguments.
Yes.
Everyone.
Currently, the student council executives
are selected by the president
and vice president.
However, in reality,
it's possible for any student to join
the student council if they want to.
In fact,
-I conducted a survey on
-Does she mean favoritism?
-former council executives.
-I think so.
Seriously?
-She even prepared this kind of data?
-Including the current student council,
-No, it wasn't Taniyama. Was it Miyamae?
-the past three student councils...
I believe
the student council should only accept
the top students who have been selected.
Don't you all feel the same way?
Students who usually have
poor grades and bad character,
the moment they become
student council executives,
they'll be above all of you.
Don't you hate that?
She's awesome as I expected.
By changing their perspective
the uninterested students
were made to see it as their own concern.
Therefore,
I propose a teacher review process.
By doing so,
we'll be able to create a student council
consisting of truly outstanding students
who are approved by the teachers.
In order to create a student council
with higher proficiency, capability,
dignity, and authority,
please cast your votes in favor.
Thank you for listening.
Next,
let's have the opposition
present their arguments.
Yes.
How's she going to turn the tables?
No, Taniyama
is definitely going to win this.
Let's hear what
the solitary princess has to say.
The coolest version of myself in my mind.
That's right.
I'm Kujou, the student council treasurer.
Regarding this agenda,
as the student council representative,
I'll be the opposition.
Taniyama mentioned earlier
that through a teacher review system,
the student council's
authority will be elevated.
However,
I have the opposite opinion.
In fact, I believe
it will decline instead.
Why is that so?
Because it will deprive core members
of the student council,
the president and vice president,
of the right to appoint executives
of the student council.
Speaking of which, in the student council,
the parties who are most admired
and envied by students
are the president and vice president
who win through an election.
It's precisely because
they win the fierce election
and gain this position
that the school
will give them a lot of power.
The right to appoint
the student council executives
is arguably the most representative
form of authority.
Although we're only handing over
some of the authority to teachers,
is this really appropriate?
Isn't that saying
that the current student council
needs the help of the teachers
to uphold its own dignity?
This school places great importance
on student self-government.
The reason why the student council
is granted tremendous discretion
is also because of this.
If the selection
of student council executives
includes a teacher review process,
what will happen then?
Would the president and vice president
be able to let promising students
join the student council freely?
They also wouldn't be able
to turn down executives
approved by the teachers, right?
Yes.
-She's speaking her mind calmly.
-So, this
-Perfect.
-is transferring the right of appointment
-Taniyama's claim and Alya's claim
-to the teachers.
-both have their merits.
-Doesn't that mean
-We're even now.
-the council has veered off course?
Taniyama.
These aren't my ideas,
but Alya's own thoughts.
Thank you for listening.
Now, it's time for questions.
I have a question.
Go ahead.
As I was saying,
in the past few years,
all students who wanted to join
the council have become executives.
As long as there are no problems,
I think it's fine.
To prevent the standards from declining,
I think it's necessary to include
the supervision of teachers.
Shouldn't the student council president
and the vice president decide that?
Admitting that you're not good enough
and seeking help from the teachers
is also a kind of resolution.
But it's not something we can decide.
You failed because you
misjudged your opponent.
Your opponent was Alya from the start.
But you've been watching me.
Next, what will you do?
Then,
what if the president
and vice president go berserk?
Well...
But Kujou is an outsider after all, right?
What would a transfer student
know about this school?
Taniyama is better, isn't she?
So she pulled this trick?
Are they shills?
What?
Please answer.
What? What did she just say?
Hurry, I have to answer her.
But what should I say?
You did well.
Leave the rest to me.
Sorry for interrupting
in the middle of a question.
I'll take over from here.
Did you lose your voice
from talking for too long?
Come on.
That happened
because you don't usually talk much.
Well then,
for my partner who lost her voice,
I want to end this meeting
as soon as possible.
But ultimately,
is it necessary
to continue this discussion?
The moment you chose
this President Kenzaki,
your feelings were clear, right?
As you all know,
President Kenzaki used to be
an unremarkable,
sub-par student in his class.
I'll take this chance to make it clear.
President Kenzaki was a darned gloomy man
who could never be approved by teachers.
But President Kenzaki
put in a lot of effort.
He improved his grades
and honed his masculinity.
He went from a gloomy student
to a dignified student council
presidential candidate.
You all once supported him, didn't you?
President Kenzaki became
the student council president
because of this system
which allows any student
to become a student council executive
as long as they have passion.
I'll ask again.
Is there really a need
for further discussion?
The sudden tease by my junior
took me by surprise.
But if there are no more questions,
we'll move on to the final debate.
Proposition, do you agree?
What?
Hey, Sayacchi!
Alya!
Okay, we surrender.
What?
In that case,
we will reject the proposition's motion.
Are you okay with that?
Yes, I am.
Oh, dear. Sorry for any trouble
caused by my Sayaka.
Well then, the motion is rejected.
That concludes the general meeting.
What?
I'm counting on you, Masachika.
Right, leave it to me, Yuki.
When I saw those two,
I thought they were the ideal ones.
A relationship where they completely trust
one another and have each other's backs.
Those two had a deep bond
that no one could match.
It was inevitable
that I couldn't beat them.
While I was a little envious, this made me
finally give up competing against them.
That's why
when I saw those two,
I felt betrayed.
Wait!
Why?
Why is it you?
Kuze and Suou are one-of-a-kind partners.
It's because of them
that I...
That I... gave up.
Why?
If you have something to say to me,
just let it all out.
I have no right to say anything to you.
I'm such an idiot.
I believed on my own,
admired on my own,
and felt betrayed on my own.
I even threw a tantrum.
Clearly, it was all my self-conceit.
There you are.
She's crying so much.
I'm sorry, Kujou.
Leave this to me.
Well...
It's fine.
Okay? Please.
Taniyama.
Actually, I also don't know
why Kuze chose me.
But I want to live up to his expectations.
So I'll do my best.
I'll make you acknowledge me someday.
That's all.
Oh dear, Kujou is such a good girl.
Yes.
After all, she's the one chosen by Kuze.
Once you've calmed down,
you can then apologize
to Kuzecchi and Kujou.
I'll go with you.
My brother is still too naive.
If he really wanted to,
he could have ended this farce right away.
Well, it doesn't matter.
If that's all it takes,
they aren't my enemies after all.
And that naivety
will lead them to self-destruction
in the near future.
Don't you think so?
Is that so?
I think Master Masachika
and Mistress Alisa
are extraordinary.
Ayano.
Yes?
You don't understand.
You really don't get it.
Be absolutely fearless,
have full control,
darken your eye corners,
and finally, act all high and mighty
while judging others.
These are the keys to creating
the vibes of a strong opponent!
I'm really sorry.
I didn't know better.
Come on, get it together.
Why do you think I accepted
this freaking hot lighting job?
LOYALTY, RIGHTEOUSNESS
Forgive my presumption,
but may I ask you something?
What is it?
You mentioned creating
the vibes of a strong opponent.
Isn't that what the final loser does?
Also,
as I reminded you earlier,
no eating or drinking
in the lighting control room.
Ayano, clean this up.
As you wish.
Taniyama said
that she thought
you and Yuki were a unique pair.
She admired you two a lot.
That's why she gave up on the election.
I see.
I'll do my best.
I'll make Taniyama admit someday
that you didn't make a mistake
by choosing to run with me.
You're right. I'll do my best too.
Hey, can I ask you something?
Why did you choose
to run with me instead of Yuki?
The reason I led the student council
with Yuki back then
was because I couldn't refuse her request.
I did want to support her
in achieving her goal,
but I think the main reason
was that I felt guilty.
Guilty?
Maybe that's why
I always felt suffocated.
Compared to the people around me
who worked so hard
for their dreams and goals,
my motivation was pathetic.
At that time,
I often had self-deprecating thoughts.
Everyone called me
"Vice President in the Shadows,"
but in the end,
I just didn't want to be in the spotlight.
But it's different this time.
With my own free will,
I decided to run for vice president
because I want to work hard...
together with you.
So, well,
you don't have
to compare yourself to Yuki.
How should I put it?
Well, you know...
It's something along that line.
I wish you were more upfront about this.
Shut up.
Are you making fun of me?
I'm not telling you.
By the way, what about you?
What do you mean?
Why do you want to run with me?
Oh my, it's simple.
What does that mean?
It's time to go home.
All right.
By the way, Kuze,
what was that just now?
Just now?
Something about the size of my boobs.
Oh, that?
Well,
a girl I know brought it up.
And then, the person said
that you should be an E cup.
Barely right.
What?
Barely?